ACTWU's Legal Department Records 5619/017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- N.Y. Joint Board of Neckwear Workers Adlawn Enterprises, Ltd. - Insurance Fund Contributions Arbitration, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 7)
- N.Y. Joint Board of Neckwear Workers Howard Creations, Inc. - Insurance Fund Contributions Arbitration, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 8)
- N.Y. Joint Board of Neckwear Workers Belle Neckwear Co. Arbitration Re: Supply of Work, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 9)
- New England Reg. Joint Board Piece Rates, 1990 (Box 104, Folder 10)
- Neckwear Joint Board Patricio Campoverde 22-CB-6337, 1990 (Box 104, Folder 11)
- Maine Joint Board Textile Division, 1979-1986 (Box 104, Folder 12)
- New York Joint Board H. Cotler Company Case no.29-CB-8237, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 13)
- Arbitration of Manuella Ibarra's Work-Sharing Grievance, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 14)
- New York Joint Board, 1976-1987 (Box 104, Folder 15)
- Glove Cities Area Liberty Leather Corp. mad Cayadutta Tanning Co., Inc., 1985 (Box 104, Folder 16)
- Glove Cities Joint Board Tanners Assn. Contract Negotiations, 1987-1988 (Box 104, Folder 17)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board Tanners Association Negotiations, 1985-1987 (Box 104, Folder 18)
- Greater Northern Joint Board, 1983-1993 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Omnicology, Inc. Gloversville, N.Y., 1984-1987 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- Glove Cities Area Liberty Leather Corp. Cayadutta Negotiations, 1980-1986 (Box 105, Folder 3)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board R.L. Kilmer & Sons, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 4)
- Glove Cities Joint Board 3-RC-8618 (Embossing), 1985-1986 (Box 105, Folder 5)
- Greater Northern Textile Joint Board (Local 3T-Delegate), 1986 (Box 105, Folder 6)
- Glove Cities Area Wood & Hyde, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 7)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board Joseph P. Conroy, Inc., 1985-1987 (Box 105, Folder 8)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board Constitutions & Bylaws, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 9)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board Fashion Tanning, 1985-1986 (Box 105, Folder 10)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board, 1975-1995 (Box 105, Folder 11)
- Pittsburgh Dist. Joint Board, 1982-1991 (Box 105, Folder 12)
- Kaufman's Enterprises, Inc. Case no.20-CA-20349, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 13)
- Kauffman Enterprises Case no.32-RC-2429, 2425, 1986-1987 (Box 105, Folder 14)
- Kauffman Enterprises Case no.32-CA-8340, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 15)
- Kaufman's ESOP, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 16)
- Juvenile Shoe Corporation Case no.17-CA-13459-2, 1987-1988 (Box 105, Folder 17)
- California Joint Board Kauffmans & Karl Eckl, 1986-1987 (Box 105, Folder 18)
- Kingform Cap Co., Inc. 29-CA-12825,12997, 1987-1989 (Box 105, Folder 19)
- Joseph & Feiss Contracts, 1986-1988 (Box 106, Folder 1)
- Joseph and Feiss Case no.8-CB-6140, 1987-1988 (Box 106, Folder 2)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. v. NLRB, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 3)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. v. Reeves Brothers, Inc. Joint Appendix, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. v.. NLRB, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  Pages 9654-1104 October 16,1987
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. v. NLRB, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  Pages 677-964 October 15, 1987
- Reeves Brothers Inc. v. NLRB, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  Pages 386-481 September 24, 1987
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. v. NLRB, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  Pages 1-177 September 22, 1987
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. v. NLRB Transcript of Testimony, 1987 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. v. NLRB Charging Party's Brief Copies, 1987 (Box 107, Folder 2)
- Third Constitutional Convention, 1984 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  June 11-15, 1984
- Convention 87- Election Material, 1987 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- Convention Committee on Pensions (Apparel), 1981 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- ACTWU Convention Detroit, Michigan, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  6/1-5 1981
- Convention, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 7)
- 1984 Convention Constitutional Amendments (Box 107, Folder 8)
- 1984 Convention Law and Constitution Committee (Box 107, Folder 9)
- 1984 Convention Elections (Box 107, Folder 10)
- Convention Election Tellers Committee, 1984 (Box 107, Folder 11)
- Minimum Dues, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 12)
- 1984 Convention (Box 107, Folder 13)
- GEB Convention Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 107, Folder 14)
- 1984 Convention Legal Dept. Report for GEB (Box 107, Folder 15)
- 1984 Convention (Box 107, Folder 16)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Contempt Proceedings, 1985-1986 (Box 107, Folder 17)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Refusal to Furnish Info., 1984-1987 (Box 107, Folder 18)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Refusal to Supply Information, 1985-1987 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Robert Generette Seniority Race Arbitration [folder 1 of 3], 1986-1987 (Box 108, Folder 2)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Robert Generette Seniority Race Arbitration [folder 2 of 3], 1985 (Box 108, Folder 3)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Robert Generette Seniority Race Arbitration [folder 3 of 3], 1985 (Box 108, Folder 4)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Hourly Employee Listing, 1986 (Box 108, Folder 5)
- Wellman Industries, Inc., 1986 (Box 108, Folder 6)
- Robert Generette - Grievance no.147, 1985 (Box 108, Folder 7)
- Betty Ruth Daniels - Grievance no.164, 1983-1986 (Box 108, Folder 8)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Case no.11-CA-11825-2 Unilateral Change in Truck Drivers Pay Rates and Grades, 1985-1986 (Box 108, Folder 9)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Unilateral Change in Truck Driver Pay Rate, 1985-1986 (Box 108, Folder 10)
- Wellman Industries Negotiations, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 11)
- Wellman Industries Bargaining, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 12)
- Wellman Industries Negotiations Proposals, 1983-1984 (Box 108, Folder 13)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Wage and Benefit Reopener, 1985-1986 (Box 108, Folder 14)
- Wellman Industries, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 108, Folder 15)
- Wellman Industries, 1983-1985 (Box 108, Folder 16)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Report, 1986 (Box 108, Folder 17)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Employee Handbook, 1954 (Box 108, Folder 18)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Katherine Belin Grievance, 1985 (Box 108, Folder 19)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Levern Graham Job Assignment Grievance, 1985 (Box 108, Folder 20)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. David Lee Miller Job Assignment Grievance, 1985 (Box 108, Folder 21)
- Wellman Industries Case no.11-CA-11655, 1985-1986 (Box 108, Folder 22)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Fairy Lee Bartell Grievance Supervisors Doing Unit Work, 1985 (Box 108, Folder 23)
- Notes re:Wellman, 1985 (Box 108, Folder 24)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. James Hayward Title VII Case, 1986 (Box 108, Folder 25)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Job Evaluation Grievance, 1986 (Box 108, Folder 26)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Open Door Policy, 1985 (Box 108, Folder 27)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Miscellaneous Matters, 1986 (Box 108, Folder 28)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Chronological File [folder 1 of 3], 1985-1986 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Chronological File [folder 2 of 3], 1984-1985 (Box 109, Folder 2)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Chronological File [folder 3 of 3], 1985 (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Wellman Industries Strategy Session, 1985 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- Wellman Industries Memos, 1984-1986 (Box 109, Folder 5)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. James Hayward Seniority Grievance., 1985-1986 (Box 109, Folder 6)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Job Reevaluations, 1986 (Box 109, Folder 7)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Joann Filyaw Constructive Discharge Arbitration, 1985-1986 (Box 109, Folder 8)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Doris Cannon Seniority Grievance, 1985 (Box 109, Folder 9)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. OSHA Matters, 1985-1986 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Resignation from Union Membership, 1980-1985 (Box 109, Folder 11)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Potential Corporated Campaign, 1985 (Box 109, Folder 12)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Karen Munnerlyn Write-Up, 1985 (Box 109, Folder 13)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Karen Munnerlyn Plant Rule Grievance, 1985 (Box 109, Folder 14)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Elise Wright and Frances Miller Rule Change, 1985 (Box 109, Folder 15)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Case #11-CA-11825-1 Karen Munnerlyn Rule Change, 1985 (Box 109, Folder 16)
- Wellman Industries, Inc. Peter Jacobs Discharge Arbitration, 1982-1983 (Box 109, Folder 17)
- Cannon Pension Plan Bill Patterson's File, 1982-1990 (Box 109, Folder 18)
- Cannon Mills Statements, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- Cannon Pension Plan, 1984-1989 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- Witness- Summary Notes, 1983 (Box 110, Folder 3)
- David Adams et al- John Cannon, Steve Addison, 1985-1986 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Virginia McIntyre, 1985-1986 (Box 110, Folder 6)
- Bobby Kemp, 1985-1986 (Box 110, Folder 7)
- Cannon Mills Newspaper Clippings, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 8)
- Cannon Mills, 1984 (Box 110, Folder 9)
- Cannon Mills Company, 1976-1983 (Box 110, Folder 10)
- Cannon Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-10021, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 11)
- Cannon Mills Company, Inc. Case no.11-CA-11892, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 12)
- Cannon Mills Case no.11-RC-3212, 1985-1986 (Box 110, Folder 13)
- Cannon Mills (Mike Curb), 1985 (Box 110, Folder 14)
- Cannon Mills, 1984-1985 (Box 110, Folder 15)
- Cannon Mills Fieldcrest, 1986 (Box 110, Folder 16)
- Cannon Mill (Settlement File), 1986 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Alj's Decision Cannon Mills, 1982-1984 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Cannon Mills Subpoena, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Cannon Mills Co, Inc. Case no.11-CA-11892, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Complaint-Ans-Charge, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Cannon Mills Co, Inc., 1986 (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Cannon Mills Legal Summary, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 7)
- Cannon Mills Co., a wholly owned subsidiary of Fieldcrest Mills, Inc. Benny McIntyre, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- ACTWU, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 9)
- Plant 5500 Actuarial Reports, 1982-1984 (Box 111, Folder 10)
- Cannon Mills (Bobby Kemp) Case no.11-CA-11806, 1985-1986 (Box 111, Folder 11)
- Ken Underwood, 1985-1986 (Box 111, Folder 12)
- Cannon Mills Newspapers, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 13)
- Cannon Mills, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 14)
- Cannon Mills Bobby Kemp Discharge, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 15)
- Copies of Leaflets (Union Leaflets), 1984 (Box 111, Folder 16)
- Cannon Mills Company, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 111, Folder 17)
- Cannon Mills Case no.11-RC-5314, 1984-1985 (Box 111, Folder 18)
- Cannon Mills, 1984-1985 (Box 111, Folder 19)
- Cannon Mills China Towels, 1982-1985 (Box 111, Folder 20)
- Cannon Mills, 1984-1985 (Box 111, Folder 21)
- Cannon Mills, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 22)
- Murdock: Settlement, 1989 (Box 111, Folder 23)
- Cannon Mills, 1980-1982 (Box 111, Folder 24)
- Cannon Mills Ogletree & Deekins (Leaflets), 1983 (Box 111, Folder 25)
- Cannon Wiscassett Mills, Co. Case no.11-RC-5328, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 26)
- Cannon Mills, Inc. Supervisors Training Sessions, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 27)
- Cannon Mills - Affidavits, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 1)
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  Pg.1-5. 3/30/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  Pg.6-211. 3/31/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  Pg.212-457. 4/1/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  Pg.458-728. 4/2/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  Pg.729-896. 4/3/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  Pg.897-1132. 4/8/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  Pg.1133-1249. 4/9/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  Pg.1250-1446. 4/9/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  Pg.1447-1585. 4/10/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  Pg.1586-1847. 4/22/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  Pg.1848-2000. 4/23/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  Pg.2001-2047. 4/24/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  Pg.2048-2115. 5/19/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  Pg.2116-2300. 7/13/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  Pg.2301-2467. 7/13/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  Pg.2468-2700. 7/14/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  Pg.2701-2791. 7/14/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  Pg.2791-2943. 7/15/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  Pg.2944-3148. 7/27/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  Pg.3149-3450. 7/28/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  Pg.3451-3650. 7/29/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  Pg.3651-3805. 7/29/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  Pg.3806-4079. 7/30/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  Pg.4080-4187. 7/31/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  Pg.4188-4416. 8/31/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  Pg.4417-4652. 9/1/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  Pg.4653-4893. 9/2/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  Pg.4894-5176. 9/3/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  Pg.5177-5296. 9/4/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  Pg.5297-5485. 10/26/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  Pg.5486-5649. 10/27/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  Pg.5650-5972. 10/28/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  Pg.5973-6260. 10/29/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  Pg.6261-6368. 10/30/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  P.6369-6498. 11/16/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  P.6499-6686. 11/16/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  P.6687-6944. 11/17/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  P.6945-7121. 11/18/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  P.7122-7297. 11/18/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  P.7298-7532. 11/19/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  p.7533-7688. 12/1/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1992 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  P.768-7749. 12/2/1992
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14494,14464, etc., 1993 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  P.7750-7839. 1/25/1993
- Goody's, Inc. Knoxville Bond Issues, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 1)
- Goody's Inc. Case no.10-CA-25862, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 2)
- Goody's Inc. Georgia Actions, 1993-1994 (Box 115, Folder 3)
- Goody's Inc. Case no.10-RC-14195, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 4)
- Goody's Family Clothing, Inc. Case #10-CA-26612, 1992-1993 (Box 115, Folder 5)
- Goody's, Inc. Leafletting Research/ CA Case, 1992-1993 (Box 115, Folder 6)
- Goody's Inc. Virginia Arrest (David Greenlief), 1993 (Box 115, Folder 7)
- Goody's Inc. Boycott, 1992-1993 (Box 115, Folder 8)
- Goody's Inc. Case no.10-CA-26718 Safety Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 115, Folder 9)
- Goody's Inc. Wage Increase 11 10-CA-26841, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 10)
- Goody's / ADA, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 11)
- Goody's Family Clothing, Inc. Case no.10-CA-27095, 1993-1994 (Box 115, Folder 12)
- Goody's Family Clothing Case no.10-CA-26240 & 26288, 1992-1994 (Box 115, Folder 13)
- Goody's Family Clothing, Inc. Case no.10-CA-26778, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 14)
- Goody's Inc. Case no.9-CB-8377, 1992-1993 (Box 115, Folder 15)
- Goody's Inc. Tennessee Actions, 1992-1994 (Box 115, Folder 16)
- Goody's Town & Country vs. ACTWU Knoxville, TN, 1993-1995 (Box 116, Folder 1)
- Goody's Inc. Case no.10-CA-26778 Leaflettings, 1993-1995 (Box 116, Folder 2)
- Goody's Family Clothing, Inc. Negotiations, 1993-1994 (Box 116, Folder 3)
- Health-Tex, 1985-1990 (Box 116, Folder 4)
- Health-Tex Legal Research, 1990 (Box 116, Folder 5)
- Health-Tex Arbitration, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 1)
- Health-Tex Outsourcing, 1990 (Box 117, Folder 2)
- Health-Tex Demand for Arbitration, 1987-1990 (Box 117, Folder 3)
- Health-Tex Newsclips, 1990 (Box 117, Folder 4)
- Health-Tex, Inc. Books, 1990 (Box 117, Folder 5)
- Health-Tex Case #2-CA-24422, 1990 (Box 117, Folder 6)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Co., Inc., 1990 (Box 117, Folder 7)
- Health-Tex Fraud Conveyance Complaint, 1990 (Box 117, Folder 8)
- Health-Tex NLRB Table of Contents Table of Contents, 1990 (Box 117, Folder 9)
- Health-Tex Pleadings, NLRB Table of Contents, 1990 (Box 117, Folder 10)
- Health-Tex Arbitration Award, 1990 (Box 117, Folder 11)
- Health-Tex Industries Shareholders' Agreement, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 12)
- Health-Tex Research, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 1)
- Health-Tex, Inc. Case no.2-CA-24422, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 2)
- Health-Tex, Inc. Arbitration Award, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 3)
- ACTWU vs. Health-Tex, Inc. No. 87 Civ.0868, 1987 (Box 118, Folder 4)
- Health-Tex Federal District Court, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 5)
- Health-Tex, Inc. Evidence, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 1)
- Health-Tex Bank Deal, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 2)
- Health-Tex (Company Documents), 1990 (Box 119, Folder 3)
- Health-Tex Arbitration Chronological Order, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 4)
- Health-Tex Rhode Island Work Stoppage, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 5)
- Health-Tex Press, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 6)
- Health-Tex Evidence, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 7)
- Health-Tex Research/Drafts, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 8)
- Health-Tex Bills, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 9)
- Health-Tex Demand for Arbitration, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 1)
- Health-Tex Memos, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 2)
- Health-Tex Inc. [folder 1 of 2], 1985-1989 (Box 120, Folder 3)
- Health-Tex, Inc. [folder 2 of 2], 1989-1990 (Box 120, Folder 4)
- Health-Tex, Inc., 1990 (Box 120, Folder 5)
- Health-Tex, Inc., 1990 (Box 120, Folder 6)
- Health-Tex Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 7)
- Health-Tex, Inc. Outsourcing, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 8)
- Health-Tex, Inc. Outsourcing, 1990 (Box 121, Folder 1)
- Health-Tex, Inc. Research, 1990 (Box 121, Folder 2)
- Health-Tex Draft Agreements, 1989-1992 (Box 121, Folder 3)
- Health-Tex, Inc. Shrinkman File, 1990 (Box 121, Folder 4)
- Doris A. Green v. Health-Tex, Inc., 1990 (Box 121, Folder 5)
- Henry E. Mann v. ACTWU Formal Papers, 1994-1995 (Box 121, Folder 6)
- Henry E. Mann v. ACTWU Memos and Bills, 1994-1995 (Box 122, Folder 1)
- Mann Deposition Outline, 1994 (Box 122, Folder 2)
- Mann v. ACTWU Miscellaneous Documents, 1988-1992 (Box 122, Folder 3)
- Mann v. ACTWU Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 122, Folder 4)
- Mann v. ACTWU Transcripts, 1994-1995 (Box 122, Folder 5)
- Mann, Henry, 1985-1986 (Box 122, Folder 6)
- Piedmont-Carolina Joint Board Local 1355 (Fletcher, N.C.) Financial Irregularities, 1991 (Box 122, Folder 7)
- Piedmont Carolinas Joint Board, 1989-1993 (Box 122, Folder 8)
- Piedmont Carolinas Joint Board Rock Hill, S.C. Paperwork Re: Denial of Tax Exempt Status, 1989 (Box 122, Folder 9)
- Union Liability Insurance, 1993-1994 (Box 122, Folder 10)
- Henry Mann v. ACTWU Memos, 1994-1995 (Box 122, Folder 11)
- Henry Mann v. ACTWU Documents, 1994 (Box 122, Folder 12)
- Henry Mann v. ACTWU Piedmont Carolinas Administratorship, 1993 (Box 122, Folder 13)
- ACTWU Grand Jury Investigation, 1992 (Box 123, Folder 1)
- Piedmont Carolinas Joint Board Misc., 1988-1989 (Box 123, Folder 2)
- Piedmont Carolinas Joint Board Administratorship, 1991-1994 (Box 123, Folder 3)
- Henry Mann ACTWU Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 123, Folder 4)
- Piedmont Carolinas Joint Board Grand Jury Subpoena, 1991-1992 (Box 123, Folder 5)
- Piedmont Carolinas District Administratorship, 1991-1992 (Box 123, Folder 6)
- Piedmont Carolinas Joint Board D.O.L., 1988-1989 (Box 123, Folder 7)
- Health-Tex Correspondence, 1990 (Box 123, Folder 8)
- Health-Tex Congress Agreements, 1990 (Box 123, Folder 9)
- Mann v. ACTWU South Carolina Research, 1993-1995 (Box 123, Folder 10)
- Mann v. ACTWU Docs from S. Reg. Joint Board File, 1988-1993 (Box 123, Folder 11)
- Mann v. ACTWU Executive Board Minutes, 1987-1992 (Box 123, Folder 12)
- Mann v. ACTWU Piedmont Carolinas District of the Southern Regional Joint Board, 1991-1992 (Box 124, Folder 1)
- Piedmont Carolinas Administratorship Bond Claim (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 124, Folder 2)
- Piedmont Carolinas Administratorship Bond Claim (2 of 2), 1989-1992 (Box 124, Folder 3)
- Mann v. ACTWU Procedural Correspondence Re: Administrative Hearing, 1991-1992 (Box 124, Folder 4)
- Mann v. ACTWU U.S. Attorney Columbia, S.C., 1991-1992 (Box 124, Folder 5)
- Henry Mann Trial, 1992-1993 (Box 124, Folder 6)
- Mann v. ACTWU Piedmont District By-Laws, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 7)
- Mann v. ACTWU Southern Region Documents, 1983-1990 (Box 124, Folder 8)
- Mann v. ACTWU Documents, 1991-1992 (Box 124, Folder 9)
- ACTWU Depositions Case no.87-CP-46-283 [folder 1 of 3], 1987-1988 (Box 124, Folder 10)
- ACTWU Depositions Case no.87-CP-46-283 [folder 2 of 3], 1988 (Box 124, Folder 11)
- ACTWU Depositions Case no.87-CP-46-283 [folder 3 of 3], 1988 (Box 124, Folder 12)
- Highland Yarn Mills Case no.11-CA-14868, 1993 (Box 124, Folder 13)
- ACTWU Depositions Case no.87-CP-46-283 [folder 1 of 2], 1992 (Box 124, Folder 14)
- ACTWU Depositions Case #87-CP-46-283 [folder 2 of 2], 1992 (Box 124, Folder 15)
- Highland NLRB Affidavits, 1991-1992 (Box 124, Folder 16)
- Highland Yarn Mills Case no.11-CA-15224, 1992 (Box 124, Folder 17)
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-15111, 1992-1993 (Box 124, Folder 18)
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-15103, 1992 (Box 124, Folder 19)
- ACTWU v. Highland Yarn Mills Charging Party's Brief [folder 1 of 2], 1992 (Box 125, Folder 1)
- ACTWU v. Highland Yarn Mills Charging Party's Brief [folder 2 of 2], 1992 (Box 125, Folder 2)
- NLRB Subpoenas, 1992 (Box 125, Folder 3)
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Employee Statements [folder 1 of 2], 1991 (Box 125, Folder 4)
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Employee Statements [folder 2 of 2], 1991 (Box 125, Folder 5)
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Affidavits and Notes [folder 1 of 3], 1992 (Box 125, Folder 6)
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Affidavits and Notes [folder 2 of 3], 1992 (Box 125, Folder 7)
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Affidavits and Notes [folder 3 of 3], 1992 (Box 125, Folder 8)
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-15111, 1993 (Box 125, Folder 9)
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Contract Agreement, 1989 (Box 125, Folder 10)
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Florence Hill v. Texfi et. Al [folder 1 of 2], 1995 (Box 125, Folder 11)
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Florence Hill v. Texfi et. Al [folder 2 of 2], 1992-1994 (Box 125, Folder 12)
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-15338, 1993 (Box 125, Folder 13)
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-15224, 1992 (Box 125, Folder 14)
- Highland Yarn Mills OSHA Case, 1992-1993 (Box 125, Folder 15)
- Highland Yarn Mills Decert and ULPs 11-CA-14814, 1992-1994 (Box 126, Folder 1)
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-15757, 1993-1994 (Box 126, Folder 2)